Open the project file .
First, add a name line for the model.
Cloud图库 provides a number of standard name lines.
Click .
You can see that there are several standard name lines here.
Click the preview icon in the upper right corner.
You can preview the name line style.
Double-click on the name line.
Add an object window.
You can also come to .
Click .
Find the name line you need in the mall.
Download and use.
You can also double-click to add an object window.
After adding the name line to the object window,
I will explain how to add a name line.
In the tool bar,
find the line name line tool and click .
The mouse wheel stops on the outside or inside line of the name line to be added.
Click .
Left-click to add a name line.
Note that once you click, you can add a name line.
If you click multiple times, you will generate multiple names.
Left-click to long-click on the name line tool.
It shows that there are three tools to add names.
Line name line, free name line, sewing line name line.
The text at the back is the corresponding shortcut.
Switch to the free name line tool.
Choose the name line to be added to the object window.
The mouse wheel stops on the outside or inside line of the name line.
There will be a blue dot.
Click and move the mouse wheel in the direction of the line.
At the end, click again to complete the free name line.
Switch to the sewing line name line.
The tool can create a name line based on the sewing line.
At this time, all the sewing lines of the name line will be displayed in the 2D window.
The mouse wheel stops on the sewing line.
A pair of blue points will appear.
Click and move the mouse wheel in the direction of the sewing line.
At the end, click again to complete the sewing line name line.
You can see that both sewing lines have created a name line.
The newly created name line is default to the selected state.
It shows a bright red in the 2D window.
Note that the corner of the board is added to the name line.
There will be an intersection here.
If you want to delete the name line, you can use the edit name line on the name line tool.
Press Shift to select multiple names.
Right-click to select Delete or Delete.
Here, use the free name line tool to complete the name line addition.
You can see that there is no intersection at the corner of the board.
Similarly, the name line at the corner of the board is also added with the free name line tool.
To edit the name line tool, you can also edit the name line position and length.
Select the tool.
At the end of the name line, press the left button and move the mouse.
You can adjust the length of the name line.
Right-click on the name line line.
Select the name line of the entire line.
Press the left button and move the mouse.
You can move the name line position.
At this time, the attribute editor will display the attribute of the selected name line.
Here you can change the type of the selected name line.
Here only shows the name line type of the object window.
You can also drag the name line in the object window to the name line on the 2D board to replace the name line.
When extending only when the starting point or end point of the name line is not reached or beyond the board's outer line,
you can open the opening or ending and extend it to the board's outer line.
Here you can choose randomly.
The curve under the turning corner can be set to be a round shape at the turning corner.
The right corner can be set to be a right-angle shape at the turning corner.
Smoothness can make the name line naturally extend at the edge and make it continuous and smooth.
According to the distance of the Z-axis, you can set the vertical distance between the name line and the board in the plane.
If you want to define the design of the name line,
you can select the name line to be customized in the object window.
In the property editor,
First, enter the name of the name line, product number, and other information.
The type can be set to the name line type as text or OBJ.
OBJ is the current three-dimensional model state.
If switched to text,
the name line will be pasted on the surface of the fabric in the form of a text.
You can choose the interval distance between the name line and the board in the line.
You can also enter the designated value.
Here enter the value 1.
The number of name lines can create up to five different types of name lines.
Here choose the number of name lines to be created as 2.
Use the same specifications and materials.
Click on these two options.
You can create two types of name lines with the same specifications and materials.
When closed, you can edit the patterns and materials of each type of name line separately.
First, edit the first type of name line.
Specifications
The pattern at the bottom of the column.
There are six different name line patterns to set.
You can also add a text to define the name line pattern.
Length
Set the name line length.
SPI refers to the number of needles within one inch.
For example, SPI 14 means that there are 14 needles within one inch.
Click on the small triangle on the left to define the length.
You can also set the needle distance.
You can also set the name line length.
You can also set the thickness of the name line and support unit switching.
Under the material column, set the pattern appearance effect of the name line.
Set the color of the name line to match the color of the fabric.
To see the effect of the name line more clearly in the 3D window.
You can switch to a thick white surface.
The grid surface under the environment setting.
You can set the number of names to be displayed on the front, the back, or the whole.
The number of lines can be set.
You can also set how many roots there are in the name line of the pattern.
Distance can adjust the distance between the names.
After selecting the 3D, it will display the pressure lines of the name line in the 3D window.
At this time, switch back to the thick white surface.
You can see that the pressure marks make the effect of the name line more impressive.
When the name line type is OBJ.
The technology under multidirectional grid optimization will display the number of grid lines of the name line.
The number of grid lines can be optimized according to the input value.
To improve performance.
The same operation can be done to edit the second name line.
If you don't want to display the second name line.
Just change the number of names here to 1.
Self-define the new name line.
If you want to apply it to the bottom and replace the original name line.
You can use the edit name line tool.
Select the name line at the bottom.
Click on the application key behind the new name line.
New name line replacement completed.
According to the effect, the name line of the model will be added to complete.
Finally, select the new name line in the object window.
Click on the save in the attribute editor.
The self-defined name line will be saved as SST format.
Convenient for next use.
Next.
In the name line position.
Add the seam to optimize the appearance details.
In the 2D tool bar.
Below the name line tool.
Related tools for sewing wrinkles.
In the line section of the sewing wrinkle tool.
Long press.
Will display three sewing wrinkles tools.
Line cut sewing wrinkles.
Free sewing wrinkles and sewing line sewing wrinkles.
Adding and deleting sewing wrinkles.
The operation method is the same as the name line.
There is no more count.
Adding sewing wrinkles.
The position is dark purple.
Add sewing wrinkles.
Next.
Everyone works with me.
Add the sewing wrinkles here.
Complete.
After adding.
Need to change the sewing wrinkle pattern.
At this time.
The object window will automatically switch to the sewing wrinkle column.
Select the default sewing wrinkle.
In the attribute editor.
The name of the sewing wrinkle.
Reprocess or rename.
The material can be from cotton.
Dining cloth.
Leather.
Nylon and Dylen.
5 types of fabrics.
In the sewing wrinkle type selection.
Select the leather corresponding to the fabric type.
The pattern can also be applied to the sewing wrinkle.
And change its color.
The hair line is blue.
Adjust the strength of the hair line.
To enhance the effect of sewing wrinkle.
Not transparent.
Used to adjust the transparency of the sewing wrinkle pattern.
The density under the specifications can be set.
The density of the sewing wrinkle.
Can be seen in the 3D window.
Width can be set to the width of the sewing wrinkle.
The sewing wrinkle pattern is set to complete.
Select the editor.
Sewing wrinkle tool.
Select the sewing wrinkle of a certain section.
The position is highlighted in purple.
Adjust its length and position.
The operation is the same as the name line.
In the attribute editor.
Extend.
The place where the wrinkle begins or ends.
Extend to the 2D panel line.
The fabric can adjust the sewing wrinkle.
And add the distance between the positions.
You can also choose to include or exclude the width of the sewing wrinkle in the fabric.
According to the Z-axis distance.
Can adjust the vertical distance between the sewing wrinkle and the panel.
Finally, the finished sewing wrinkle is saved.
The object window selects it.
In the attribute editor, click Save.
The sewing wrinkle is saved in the PTP file format.
You can use it later.